{
    "subject": "resource/Llu\u00eds_Mart\u00ednez_Sistach",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Catalonia",
    "human_readable": "Llu\u00eds Martinez Sistach was born in Catalonia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9263830780982971,
            "question": "Where was Llu\u00eds Martinez Sistach born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6099587082862854,
            "question": "Can you name other famous individuals born in Catalonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.427033007144928,
            "question": "Is there anything else you know about Llu\u00eds Martinez Sistach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35688790678977966,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Catalonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32416704297065735,
            "question": "What region is Catalonia known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32280921936035156,
            "question": "Does Llu\u00eds Martinez Sistach have any notable achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2892085313796997,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the culture of Catalonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19876042008399963,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist destinations in Catalonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05476043373346329,
            "question": "What is the significance of birthplace in someone's identity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.013325034640729427,
            "question": "How does geography influence a person's life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Llu\u00eds Martinez Sistach was born in Catalonia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5548_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of birthplace in someone's identity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5548_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular tourist destinations in Catalonia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5548_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the culture of Catalonia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5548_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5548_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5548_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5548_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5548_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5548_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5548_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5548_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5548_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5548_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5548_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Llu\u00eds Mart\u00ednez Sistach, including his birthplace. Specifically, the document states that he was \"born 29 April 1937 in Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain,\" which supports the statement that Llu\u00eds Mart\u00ednez Sistach was born in Catalonia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}